yourdegreecenter.com 2011-12-31

# YourDegreeCenter.com

| 

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
Last Updated: August 1, 2007

YourDegreeCenter.com is operated by VintageMediaDirect, Inc.

This Privacy Policy covers this vintagemediadirect.com Web site, which is owned and operated by VintageMediaDirect.com, LLC. ("Vintage Media Direct," "We," "Us," or "Our"). 

Before you submit any information to Our Web site, please read this Privacy Policy for an explanation of how We will handle your information. By using any part of Our Web site, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use Our Web site.

**WHAT IS OUR COMMITMENT TO YOU?**  
We are sensitive to your privacy concerns, and are committed to letting you know what Information is being collected on Our Web site, how the Information is being used and what choices you have regarding the collection and use of the Information. Please take a moment to review this Privacy Policy and contact Us with any questions. 

**PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**  
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If We decide to make material changes to Our privacy policy, We will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places We deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information We collect, how We use it, and under what circumstances, if any, We disclose it.  We encourage you to review this Web site from time to time to review changes to Our Privacy Policy.   
**  
WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND WHY?**  
We gather personally identifiable information (PII) that you expressly provide when you enter information into Our forms to request information on educational institutions.  We collect information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, and other unique personal identifiers (e.g., education level, etc.) ("Personal Information"). If you choose not to provide the requested Personal Information, We may not be able to offer you personalized services that require such information.

| 

We also use log files to collect anonymous information, which includes any information that is not tied to your Personal Information, such as your IP address ("Anonymous Information"). You are not required to register on Our Web site in order for Us to collect Anonymous Information about you. In addition, We may receive information about you from other sources including, but not limited to, service providers for tracking and marketing purposes ("Source Information"). Source Information may consist of referral data or the Web site you were previously visiting prior to visiting Our Web site; and information related to the browser and/or platform you are using to access Our Web site. Personal Information, Anonymous Information, and Source Information are collectively referred hereinafter as "Information." 

In addition to the Information that you provide to Us or that We obtain about you, We will also collect certain information arising out of your use of Our Web site, or augment the data We collect with other information from other online or offline sources. We use "cookies" and the Information to enhance your experience and present you with personalized offers. Likewise, We may use third-party advertising companies to serve and track advertisements appearing on Our Web site. Such third-party companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. To learn more about "cookies," please see the section below titled "Cookies and Log Files". We have no access or control over these third party cookies.

**SUPPLEMENTAL USE OF INFORMATION**  
In order to provide better service to you, any personal information you've submitted to us may, on occasion, be supplemented with information from third party sources both online and offline. In addition, information collected online may be stored with information collected from other sources, including offline sources.

**COOKIES AND LOG FILES**  
A cookie is a small piece of information that many Web sites use to help make shopping online easier. The information is stored on your computer's hard drive and provides a number of conveniences for you. We set and access cookies on your computer to provide you with customized content and to assist in providing the services that you have requested. Most cookies are "session cookies," which automatically delete themselves from your hard drive after each session. Like many Web sites, We automatically track aggregate information based upon your behavior on Our Web sites. We combine information that We obtain through the use of cookies with other aggregate or anonymous data, including a unique ID We may assign you. As described above, We use this information for research purposes to better understand, protect and service Our customers. The information We track may include such information as browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, IP address and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer Our Web sites, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

We do link your personally identifiable information to Our cookies. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site.  We have no access to or control over these cookies.   
If you want to prevent a third-party advertising network from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, you may wish to alter the cookie settings within your browser. Please review the instructions for your browser on how this is performed. Please see "Offering You Choices-Marketing Options" above for information on how to opt-out of sharing your Information.

We collect non-personally identifiable Information about you via Our use of Log Files and Cookies to (a) provide products, programs, and services that you have requested; (b) operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by Us and Our affiliated companies, successors, and assigns; (c) personalize the content and advertisements provided to you; (d) conduct research about your use of the features, offerings and content from Us, Our parent or sister companies and partners; (e) provide product improvement; (f) "pre-populate" forms; (h) provide you with advertising targeted to your preferences; and (g) help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest to you. 

We collect aggregate Information that is not personally identifiable and store that information in Log Files, Such information may include, without limitation, information about the different sites that you visit on the Internet, the time and frequency at which you visit them and the content that you transmit or post on other Web sites.

If you do not want Us to collect information, do not input any data on Our Web site.

  **WITH WHOM WILL THE INFORMATION BE SHARED?**  
We may share Information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies or for particular purposes including, without limitation, the purposes described below. In all cases, you may opt-out of sharing your Information with such providers by choosing not to use or register for that service or content. Please see "Offering You Choices-Marketing Options" below for information on how to opt-out of sharing your Information. 

  * Products or Service Requests - If you submit a request for a product or service on Our Web site, We will share Information about you contained in the request form with Our business partners (such as a University) to process and fulfill your request. Our business partners may contact you by telephone, e-mail, or mail based on the Information you provided to Us, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission, any state equivalent Do Not Call List, or the Do Not Call List of a specific company. If one of Our business partners contacts you by telephone and you wish not to be contacted again by that business partner with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that partner not to contact you again. 
  * Subsidiaries, Parent, or Sister Companies: We may share Information about you with Our subsidiaries, sister companies, parent company, successors, and assigns unless you opt-out of sharing Information with such parties. Please see "Offering You Choices - Marketing Options" below for information on how to opt-out of sharing your Information. 
  * Required by Law: We may also share Information about you as permitted or required by law including, without limitation, inquires by law enforcement or to comply with Federal laws including, without limitation, the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 ("CAN-SPAM Act of 2003"). We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when We believe that disclosure is necessary to protect Our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Our Web site.

**OFFERING YOU CHOICES - MARKETING OPTIONS**  
If you sign up on Our Web site to receive more information regarding any school, signing up as an affiliate, or register as a vendor you will receive promotional emails from Us.  However, you have choices when it comes to learning about new offers or services. If you do not wish to receive offers of products or services from Us, Our sister companies, or partners, here are the methods you may employ to opt-out: 

  * E-mail Opt-out Options: Each marketing e-mail We send includes instructions and an unsubscribe link. 
  * Refusing Cookies: Subject to the section below pertaining to cookies, you have the ability to prohibit being served an advertisement based on cookie technology. We utilize reputable third-party vendors to serve advertisements. If however, you are not comfortable with cookies, you can adjust the settings within your browser to further prohibit being served a cookie. Please see the browser's instructions to perform this task. 

Please note that suppressed contact information will not be used for any other purpose except to ensure compliance with your opt-out request and to comply with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 and any other applicable state and/or Federal laws regarding your choices when it comes to commercial marketing.   
**  
DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLY TO OTHER WEB SITES?**  
Our Web site may contain links to non-Vintage Media Direct Web sites. We believe such other Web sites share a similar commitment to consumer privacy and urge you to review their privacy policy when visiting their Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other Web sites.   
  
**TRANSFERABILITY OF INFORMATION**  
Information collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy by Us may be stored and processed within the United State of America or in any other country in which We or Our agents maintain facilities. By using Our Web site, you consent to any transfer of Information outside of your country, should We find it necessary. 

In the event that We are acquired or merge with another company, or upon a sale of all or portion of Our assets, Information about you will be among the assets transferred to the new company. You will be notified via prominent notice on Our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. The new company may handle such Information in accordance with its own policies and procedures and not in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**SECURITY**  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, We cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**COMMUNICATIONS FROM THE SITE**  
From time to time We may send service related communications from Our site including welcome emails and validations emails. You may not opt-out of receiving these emails if you have opted to receive special offers or promotional materials, you will receive those via email. You would have the opportunity to unsubscribe from these emails by following the instructions in each special offer or promotional email. 

**SERVICE RELATED ANNOUNCEMENTS**  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.  For instance, if Our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, We might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.  If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

**ACCESS TO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing Our Customer Support at inquiry@vintagemediadirect.com or by contacting Us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

**A SPECIAL NOTE REGARDING PEOPLE UNDER 18 YEARS OLD**  
Individuals under the age of eighteen (18) should not send any Information to Us. Each time you access Our Web site, or provide Information about yourself or anyone else, you are representing to Us that you are eighteen (18) years or older. 

**CONTACTING VINTAGEMEDIADIRECT**  
If you have questions about Our Privacy Policy, please contact us.

Vintage Media Direct  
302 Washington Street, Ste 1108  
San Diego, CA 92103
